Guide to the Albert R. Mann Library exhibition materials,1994-2007.
Mann, Albert R. Library exhibition materials, 1994-2007
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Albert R. Mann Library exhibition materials, 1994-2007.
13-18-3601
Cornell University. Albert R. Mann Library.
4.5 cubic ft.
Printed Materials, Publications, Photographs.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Division exhibit items, records and related material. The collection contains text, book lists and materials used in exhibits displayed at Mann Library from 1994-2007.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Division exhibit items, records and related material. The collection contains text, book lists and materials used in exhibits displayed at Mann Library from 1994-2007.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Albert R. Mann Library.; Albert R. Mann Library--Exhibitions.
Subjects:
Library exhibits.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Printed Texts and Plans 2001-2007
  - Printed Texts and Plans 2001-2007 (Box 1)
- Series II. Early Mann Exhibits 1994-2001
  - Lace Exhibit (date unknown) (Box 2)
  - CALS Deans Exhibit 1994-1995 (?), Pt. 1 (Box 2)
  - CALS Deans Exhibit 1994-1995 Pt. 2 (Box 2)
  - CHLHE Exhibit 2000-2001 (Core Historical Literature of Home Economics) (Box 2)
  - Kennedy Exhibit (date unknown) Pt. 1 (Box 2)
- Series III. Exhibit Materials 2001-2005
  - Kenneday Exhibit Pt. 2 (Box 2)
  - 1791 William Prince Catalogs Fruit Oct. 2001-Feb. 2002 (Box 3)
  - Abuzz ABout Bees Aug. 2002-Nov. 2002 (Box 3)
  - Written in Stone Nov. 2002-Feb. 2003 (Box 3)
  - Blaschka Glass Invertebrates Mar. 2003-July 2003 (Box 3)
  - Taste of Science Jan. 2004-Mar. 2004 (Box 3)
  - Mail Order Gardens June 2004-Sept. 2004 (Box 3)
  - Apple Exhibit Sept. 2005-Nov. 2005 (Box 3)
- Series IV. Exhibit Materials 2001-2003
  - An Exhilaration of Wings Jan. 2001-Mar. 2001 (Box 4)
  - Texts on Textiles Mar. 2001-June 2001 (Box 4)
  - Languages of Flowers June 2001-Aug. 2001 (Box 4)
  - Field Guides Spring 2002 (Box 4)
  - A Harvest of Freedom... May 2002-Aug. 2002 (Box 4)
  - Through the Lens Jan. 2003-Apr. 2003 (Box 4)
  - Cornell Roots Fall 2003 (Box 4)
- Series V. Exhibit Materials 2006
  - Ringwood June-Aug. 2006 (Box 5)
  - First Person Sept.-Oct. 2006 (Box 5)
- Series VI. Exhibit Materials 2004-2006
  - Aliens: Invasice Species Apr.-May 2004 (Box 6)
  - Green Hope Jan.-Mar. 2005 (Box 6)
  - Mycological Marvels May-Aug. 2005 (Box 6)
  - Meatless Nomdays... Nov. 2005-Feb. 2006 (Box 6)
  - Fast & Afforable Feb.-May 2006 (Box 6)
- Series VII. Exhibit Materials 2006-2007
  - Earth Pattern Exhibit Fall 2007 (rolled poster) (Box 7)
  - Student Expo Exhibit Spring 2006 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Behind These Walls Exhibit Summer 2006 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Chocolate: Food of the Gods Exhibit February-March 2007 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Stuff: Storage in America Exhibit April-May 2007 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Series VIII. Miscellaneous
  - MSS Folder 1 Over-size display materials